世上有两种痛苦
there are two kinds of pain
一种让人变得坚强
sort of pain that makes you strong
另一种则毫无意义
or useless pain
只是徒添痛苦而已
sort of pain that's only suffering
而我对无用之事毫无耐心
I have no patience for useless things
像这样的时刻需要一个会行动的人
moments like this require someone who will act
做不讨喜的事情
do the unpleasant thing
同时也是必要的事情
the necessary thing
我不管有多大代价
I don't care how much it hurts
我不管有多大争议
I don't care how controversial it is
你的任务，就是想办法做到
your job is to find a way
你就是靠这种方式心安理得的吗
is this how you live with yourself
把卑鄙当成体面
by rationalizing the obscene into the palatable
通往权力之路，皆以牺牲铺就
the road to power is paved with casualties
永不后悔
never regret